hello guys um today we're going to
analyze IC lomard General Insurance
company so going onto this uh chart
let's analyze in the larger time frame
and then uh let's go into the shorter
time frame for entry and exit
uh uh
points so let's go to the monthly time
frame this is how the chart looks in the
monthly time
frame and if we Analyze
This so it is forming some kind of Base
at
this uh
place and on the top um it is also
forming
this resistance
line
so uh in the February month the
resistance is broken and then it started
consolidating it's going in the sideways
for uh 3 months for the March April and
may it's completely in the sideways so
one can take an entry if the price
crosses this point like um 1,700 1740 so
one can take an entry by putting the
stop loss below this trend line as this
is a monthly time frame you can um aim
for the shorter uh stop losses let's go
to the shorter time frames so this is
how the chart looks in the daily time
frame like it has given um breakout and
it's completely moving in the
sideways so we can also draw this um
trend line resistance line we can uh
find that it's consolidating in the
channel pattern so in the weekly time
frame this is how the chart looks like
so
once if the price gives a breakout after
this as it is consolidating for the uh
very long time we can expect a huge
momentum after breaking uh from this
consolidation range
so let's discuss about the scenarios
what all scenarios can happen in the
near future so the scenario number one
be like uh price May consolidate in
between uh this zone for sometimes take
this retest of this trend line and it
can move up this is one scenario and the
scenario number two will be like uh
let's consider this as a fake out then
the price comes back into this Zone and
it can go retest this bottom line and
then again um move inside this Zone
that's one
scenario or else if you see let's draw
one more trend
line so this is one more trend line
where it is taking a quite number of uh
supports at the bottom one two three
times it has taken uh support price May
consolidate this is the conference point
so once the price touches this point we
can expect some momentum gain in this uh
stock price and it can move up that's
one thing so now let's plan um the entry
points
so once the price breaks out from this
range we can put a stop- loss below this
trend line which is uh close to 9% of
the stop loss and we can aim for uh
bigger risk reward ratios as this is a
multiyear Breakout
uh so we can aim for close
to uh 2 to three
R which is a decent gain so so for the
risk of uh 10% you can aim at
27% close to
27% so this is how this chart looks like
thank you